Maria Christine Roque

Experienced Technical Lead and Growth Manager with demonstrated history of working in the Contact Centre, Consumer Electronics and Digital Marketing industry. Highly skilled in Frontend Development, Mobile and Web App Database Management, Customer Service and Technical Support. Seasoned Freelance Professional with 10+ years of experience.

mcroque89@gmail.com

0400753725

Sandhurst, VIC

in linkedin.com/in/mcroque

WORK EXPERIENCE

Customer Growth Manager Jobs Outsourced | Sep 2019 – Present

- Managing the entire operations for this Digital Marketing Agency based in Adelaide who is servicing local and international clients
- Handling most of website builds, testing and liaising with clients

CS/Tech Support Lead Vonzeal | Nov 2019 – Present

 Monitoring helpdesk, providing tech support and overseeing parts and repairs for electronics products being manufactured and distributed by Vonzeal

Professional Freelancer Upwork Inc | Jan 2013 – Present

- Contractual jobs from various clients worldwide; such as Australia, New Zealand, Canada and the USA.
- Presently working for Indiegogo.com (and have been for the last 4 years) as a senior member of the User Operations team handling technical concerns and BBB complaints
- Established consistent workload amounting to average of 56 hours of paid work per week

Mobile and Web App Assistant Content Manager BLUESKY, Melbourne | Aug 2013 – Sep 2014

- Started with the company as a contractor in August 2013, worked remotely from the Philippines for 11 months and was hired as regular employee when I migrated to Australia in 2014
- Supervised a team of six contractors tasks delegation, escalations, performance review
- Handled management and organization of mobile and web app database, as well as content-readiness for every new app updates
- Liaised concerns to other departments and maintained effective communication towards achieving company goals

Client Technical Support DELL, Philippines | Jul 2010 - Dec 2012

- Phone, email and chat-based B2B support, handling troubleshooting, sales and care issues for small and medium businesses affiliated with DELL USA
- Handled all computer-related issues from hardware to software, accessories and function-specific-programs
- Liaised with key stakeholders regarding Dell products enquiries, troubleshooting, ordering parts, etc.
- Recorded team members' compliance for each courses and updates team board that contains team's metrics every week

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development, 2020 Monash University Melbourne, Australia

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science, 2007 Systems Technology Institute Bulacan, Philippines

SKILLS

CSS
HTML
JavaScript
Node.js
Bootstrap
Zurb Foundation
UX/UI
WordPress
InvisionApp



ACHIEVEMENTS

- Best of the Best employee for the last quarter of 2011 and first quarter of 2012
- Consistent Quarterly Performance Bonus achiever
- Top Employee for the month of June 2011
- Top Performer during training/transition

STRENGHTS

Troubleshooting Adaptability Communication

Problem-solving Efficiency Time Management

COGNITIVE TRAITS

